Hello friends, today
we are going to talk about diabetes
because trading in the market and
anything can happen to you, friends, this topic
is global health, due to which you must have taken many domestic
health insurance, Amrit,
its line family health insurance is covered,
but do you have international, then the
problem is health insurance, if not then
see the difference in the video, complete
information, so it is a process and
which plans, forget the explanation of all,
friends, let's start first of all
and this is, so friends, if you are
facing international,
or either family, individual,
or you are related to
business activity, or
such an employee, you have to do
international wait, then you should
definitely take this plan, so friends, you will
see complete information in it, which are
related to you, what is the
procedure and which are the plants, then at that
time tell the chart
related to all, for all the others, their
international 1 inch is according to a different budget  It
goes up to 2828 crores. You must have
seen that there are many international
celebrities who get a lot of
international treatment done through this plan. They have a
subscription for medical treatment or have
cancer, so they get many different
screen statements done, so different
statements are taken from international countries which have
honey batter there, you can
get a good seat, for this also this service
can update you, so friends, let's
take their introduction, first of all friends, these
plans are mainly their range
52522 front part current account and
in this it is included in globally hard countries,
you can go to any country and get
your treatment done,
I will also tell you what you have to do for that,
friends, many plans are written in it,
Global International and another additional
district, this section chapter note
is important, so if you have to input them, then
for them you have to do it
on a Bluetooth line, apart from that
friends, in the treatment you get done here, there is
no prostitution and post in it, as much as there is a
hospitalization charging point.  And in
that, you have to pay 20% of it yourself. The
premium amount is 90%.
Which is the best policy left? So,
like many companies
give you that 90% only after paying premium.
Many insurance companies keep doing 80851.
So, this plan plan, its conditions vary.
After that, friends, their
premium is
three to four times more than the domestic case, it is three
to four times multiple.
So, this decision is individual wise, like Global
Yasmin has knowledge, this type is also the same, it is a
matter of individual and family provincial
president friends, now let's see
what is their procedure. So, first of all, if
you have done this plan, then you have a
domestic medical which you do,
then 611. One,
before boarding an international flight, you have to
submit this to the company, you have to confirm
that and going for registration
treatments, so this is done friends, saffron
one and if you travel in an emergency
or it is in the emergency kit  You may have
forgotten to confirm your address, even if you have to confirm
your country, whether it is
India or American, you have to take a medical
certificate and
you cannot clear the insurance. The
second thing, friends, is in your to-do list
that you did not get a medical certificate, you just
tell it in cash like that that
you have hospitalization and your complete
treatment is done and the payment is made directly to
me. This is
not the case in international friends, so you
see, there are many
hospitals in many cities, there is a
network, it is practical for the insurance company, if you are
not so healthy then
for that, friends, I have done a complete remember
policy, so I believe that you have 20 crore rupees.
Hello friends, from this study, if
you get treatment done internationally, you will have to
pay first, then you can get remembers,
you will get a reverse mortgage, so
you will get that notification from inside
and whenever there is a post-hospitalization hospitalization, you will
not get it, so friends, you want an advantage in this that
you become mentally free, so
as a frequent traveler, do not fit some
such traveler.  If it is done, then you are
going for business work or for any other work,
right, you are completely relaxed
because friends, in these developed countries, there is a
lot of
pressure on hospitals in India, so this
can save you from back corruption
if you need global treatment or if you have
advanced treatment, you
can also take it, if you have cancer or any other
investment, then you
can look at the plan now, so now let us see that you have
a risk factor character in it, so
friends, there is the exchange rate, for
example, if you did GST treatment, then the
exchange rate you have is
cheerful and plus or minus, let us tell you about it, so
friends, now let us see, this
was a little information about
how global classes work, how they love it
and how it works, now let me
tell you which plans you
can consider for purchasing India's Blazer, so
friends, first of all, let
me tell you the name of the plant of Bajaj Allianz,
Global Personal Vehicle
Plan  The name of this is which they
give you up to Rs 22222 crore to 225 crores, which is
this accident cover back cover, the pride of gas is
open, you have health that cover,
secondly if you are mad then Aditya Birla
Planet which is called setting Diamond Ashok
Debit Helpline in which
friends this is your fast report from National,
which gives you advance or
else you just have to get data entry treatment
done, life number of power switch, you have got any
learning statement done, any surgery of 1 hour, then
more time treatment
also, they have made a list, Earring Phase
page, different tunes which are named, you
can get different treatments done, you do
not need to be fresh but you can
complete it in the refuge, so this also
reaches the duty rates in this way, so
help cricket, many apps, there is
news of day of clans in it and
you are given the option to restore hospitalization,
Aditya Birla's definition of clans, let me tell you
that you have to select the account, if you
want accident plan then there are different tests,
many daughters, you can do it with this  Apart from this, you will also get
New India Insurance, Hareli Green
Signal, many Sun Life Insurance,
it is also available in many different insurance plans after
10 inches extra cloth,
proper medical policy, money plan,
Manipal plan, so
in that many varieties, you
must also click on Royal Prince, Assets, Pregnancy of many good
companies, you can come to India by
researching and selecting your global insurance plan and
set yourself the financial
Ajay has come to the table or you can do many enemy pose, so
friends, there is use of Liberty, in
which Yellow To provide this premium up to Rs 1 crore, so
many
friends, there are varieties like Harish Sharma,
Aditya Birla, Bajaj Finance, Rally's
Oriental Insurance, New India
Insurance, any one of you like,
half inch plus, there you
can make a check international week, an incident plan and you
can express yourself and your family, there you are a frequent
international welcome, either you have any
dual citizen or any other in this way,
here you can choose whether
you are in any country for a long time or if it is a matter of
cancer  The people living in it
also need nutrients, so in such a situation, you can
secure your health and your fans by taking a
global insurance plan.
Friends, by doing this juice during pregnancy, a
person can get the benefit of Mr. Advice 19 on the network.
This is definitely an advance playlist of a financial advisor. If you
liked it, then
share it with your friends and family members,
like it and subscribe to the channel.
Thank you
[Music]
Kar Do Kar Do
A Specific Artist